Tlingit songs and texts collected by Nora Marks Dauenhauer and Richard Dauenhauer
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Tlingit and English recordings, ca. 1950-1997 Bulk: 1970-1990
  - J.B. Fawcett, 1969, Tape 388.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR284)
    Description of contents: Recorded at Marks Trail, Juneau, by Nora Florendo (Dauenhauer). From documentation: Side 1. 1) Elizabeth David, 2) J. B. Fawcett, History of Migration, 3) Final destination, Glacier Bay, 4) keelt' ayax'aak not Glacier Bay's, 5) eeshaan gushei, 6) J. B. Fawcett, Kooxkoonaaka tlein—Gunanaa, 7) J. B. Fawcett, funeral pyre song- Gunanaa, 8) J. B. Fawcett, Sht'eigaax song Gunanaa, 9) Ts'ootsxan' Side 2. 1) Jenny Marks, Chush koogaatunax datanch, 2) J. B. Fawcett, Ts'ootsxan, 3) J. B. Fawcett, Ts'ootsxan, 4) J. B. Fawcett, Ts'ootsxan, 5) J. B. Fawcett, Ts'ootsxan, 6) J. B. Fawcett, Yeil gaak'w shindaa. Detailed insert of contents dated March 4, 1986. 1969 label also notes "T'awyaat songs, Haida song," and history of granddaughter Leni Topacio's name.
  - J.B. Fawcett, 1969, Tape 389.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR285)
    Description of contents: J.B. Fawcett. Fall 1969. Recorded at Marks Trail, Juneau, by Nora Florendo (Dauenhauer). This appears to be a copy of #388, as it is labeled "copy," but the contents' insert is slightly different. To be safe, we should migrate both tapes and edit the contents inserts as we do metadata. Sides not noted on the insert. 1) Jenny Marks, Lukaax.ádi song, 2-5) J.B. Fawcett, songs, 6) J.B. Fawcett, Gunanáa, 7) J.B. Fawcett, Yeigak'w shindaa 8), Jenny Marks, Glacier Bay, 9) Story of Lukaax.ádi, names of slaves, 10) story of Ch'eet s'aaxw of Kaagwaantan, 11) story of slaves names, 12) Jenny Marks, Léix'w daak wu.eexí, 13) Jenny Marks, Agwaagadzanaa yaa gwaa hee a hee, 14) Jenny Marks, Yaa naa nei oh, ho.
  - Alfred Andrews, Jimmy Marks, Jack David, undated, Tape 391.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR286)
    Description of contents: "John Marks handwriting. Check also #160 and #283 in this archive."
  - Copy of Mrs. Davis, June 23, 1973, Tape 392.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR287)
    Description of contents: "Copies made from Carol Beery Davis's old aluminum recordings, made in her home in June 1973."
  - Copy of Carol Beery Davis recording of Jim Fox, June 27, 1973, Tape 393.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR288)
  - Copy of Carol Beery Davis recording of unknown artists, June 27, 1973, Tape 394.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR289)
    Description of contents: "Copies made from Carol Beery Davis's old aluminum recordings, made in her home in June 1973. Halibut Dance, Ptrmigan Dance, Gunanaa Dance, Halibut Spirit."
  - Harriman expedition recordings from 1899, undated, Tape 395.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR290)
    Description of contents: "'Copy of copy of EC 10' 501 accession of #83-908-F (6038A, 6039A), 1899. Recording of Tlingit on wax cylinder. Anthony Seeger of the Smithsonian Office of Folklife programs brought the wax cylinders to the attention of Dr Michael Krauss of Alaska Native Language Center, who identified the language as Tlingit and made a copy for Nora to transcribe. See HTY 156-161 for transcription and translation; 325ff for notes."
  - Song for Dick and Nora from Peter Kalifornsky, undated, Tape 396.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR291)
    Description of contents: unidentified.
  - Bertha Trifon, February 13, 1978, Tape 397.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR292)
  - Russian Old Believer Singing, July 20, 1979, Tape 398.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR293)
    Description of contents: "Maria Mametiev (?), Gervais, Oregon. Recorded by Suzy Jones. Sides A & B."
  - Russian Old Believer Singing, July 20, 1979, Tape 399.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR294)
    Description of contents: "Maria Mametiev (?), Gervais, Oregon. Recorded by Suzy Jones. Side C (and D?)."
  - Carcross Potlatch, undated, Tape 400.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR295)
    Description of contents: "Tape sides are labeled 7 and 8, so presumably there are 3 tapes missing in the series. Austin Hammond and Jenny (no last name) are written on the tape, so presumably he is the host?"
  - Shark House Practice, October 13, 1976, Tape 401.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR296)
    Description of contents: "Singers identified are David [Kadashan], drum, Elsie P[ratt], Nora D[auenhauer], Florence [Sheakley], Lilian, Ida K[adashan], William J[ohnson]."
  - Tape from Angoon, undated, Tape 403.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR297)
    Description of contents: "Source unknown. A. Side A. B. Side A (cont.). Side B. The labeling is confusing and probably refers to the sides on the original recording, probably a reel-to-reel. When doing metadata check to confirm if tapes 404 and 405 are continuations or duplicates."
  - Tape from Angoon, undated, Tape 404.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR298)
    Description of contents: "A. Side A (continued). Side B. B. Side One Tape from Angoon. It may be that this cassette begins on Side B and continues to Side A."
  - Tape from Angoon, undated, Tape 405.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR299)
    Description of contents: "A. Side One. B. Side One (cont.) Side Two."
  - Hoonah Potlatch, undated, Tape 406.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR300)
    Description of contents: "The tape is #3, so presumably 2 others in the sequence are missing."
  - Hoonah, October 8, 1988, Tape 407.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR301)
  - Hoonah, October 8, 1988, Tape 408.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR302)
    Description of contents: Tape 2.
  - Xeitl Hit, Klukwan, May 6, 1972, Tape 409.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR303)
  - Haines, undated, Tape 410.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR304)
    Description of contents: "Box labeled Ixt'. Cassette sides numbered 7 and 8. In blue ink "Haines." On side 7, in very faded red ink what seems to be xixch'ee s'aaxw. On side 8, in faded rsed ink "Haines – Jenny" and what may be leikw or keikw. Box and tape numbered #48."
  - Mrs. Jenny Klanott [Thlunaut], Chilkat Blanket, undated, Tape 411.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR305)
    Description of contents: unidentified. "Possibly in sequence with #412, as tape brand is the same."
  - Haines, April 28, 1970, Tape 412.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR306)
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 3, May 15, 1989, Tape 416.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR307)
    Description of contents: Tape 3. "Cassettes 1, 2, and 4 are currently not in the sequence. A complete set may be in the Sealaska Heritage Institute archives."
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 5, May 16, 1989, Tape 417.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR308)
    Description of contents: Tape 5.
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 6, May 16, 1989, Tape 418.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR309)
    Description of contents: Tape 6.
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 7, May 17, 1989, Tape 419.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR310)
    Description of contents: Tape 7.
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 8, May 17, 1989, Tape 420.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR311)
    Description of contents: Tape 8.
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 9, May 17, 1989, Tape 421.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR312)
    Description of contents: Tape 9.
  - Rasmussen Conference, Portland Museum, Tape 10, May 17, 1989, Tape 422.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR313)
    Description of contents: Tape 10, Final session.
  - Raven House, October 12-13, 1972, Tape 423.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR314)
    Description of contents: Side A = 102; B = 103.
  - Raven House, October 14, 1972, Tape 424.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR315)
    Description of contents: Side A = 105; B = 106.
  - Raven House, October 14, 1972, Tape 425.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR316)
    Description of contents: Side A = 107; B = 108.
  - Raven House, October 14, 1972, Tape 426.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR317)
    Description of contents: Side A = 108A; B = 108B.
  - Raven House, October 14, 1972, Tape 427.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR318)
    Description of contents: Side A = 109; B = 110.
  - Raven House, October 15, 1972, Tape 428.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR319)
    Description of contents: Side A = 111; B = 112.
  - Fritz Willard, Raven House (?), Haines, October 17-18, 1972, Tape 430.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR320)
    Description of contents: Side A = 115; B = 116.
  - Alex Marks funeral, October, 1971, Tape 435.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR321)
  - Charlie Dick 40 Day party, undated, Tape 436.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR322)
    Description of contents: "Sitka. No Date. 1. Hymn by Russian Choir; 2. Henry Benson; 3, Andrew P Johnson; 4, Mrs Linda Bailey; 5, Unidentified; 6, Esther Littlefield; 7, Mrs Perkins; 8, Mr Howard; 9, Bringing out money; 10, Mrs Joseph."
  - Nick Moses 40 Day Party, January 31, 1973, Tape 437.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR323)
    Description of contents: "Sitka?"
  - Jessy Wilson, undated, Tape 438.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR324)
  - Thunderbird Songs, November 17, 1971, Tape 439.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR325)
    Description of contents: From the Kookesh Collection.
  - Bear Tribe Song and Stories, undated, Tape 440.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR326)
  - Unidentified content, undated, Tape 441.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR327)
  - Kaagwaantaan Potlatch, Sitka, Tape 1, April 26, 1980, Tape 442.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR328)
    Description of contents: From Sergei Kan.
  - Kaagwaantaan Potlatch, Sitka, Tape 2, April 26, 1980, Tape 443.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR329)
  - Kaagwaantaan Potlatch, Sitka, Tape 3, April 26, 1980, Tape 444.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR330)
  - Testamonies for Land, 1986, Tape 445.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR331)
    Description of contents: Hoonah and Angoon.
  - Hinchman, Martin, Houston Memorial, October 9, 1974, Tape 446.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR332)
    Description of contents: Hoonah, sides I and II.
  - Hinchman, Martin, Houston Memorial, October 9, 1974, Tape 447.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR333)
    Description of contents: Hoonah, sides IV and V. Note: 446 and 447 appear to be in sequence, but sides II and III are missing or mislabeled.
  - Mamie Williams, August 11, 1972, Tape 448.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR334)
    Description of contents: Hoonah.
  - Hoonah Lodge Dedication, February 12, 1977, Tape 449.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR335)
    Description of contents: Sides 1 and 2.
  - Hoonah Lodge Dedication, February 12, 1977, Tape 450.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR336)
    Description of contents: Sides 5 and 6. Note: see #402 for sides 3 and 4 of Hoonah Lodge Dedication. Feb. 12, 1977. The tapes were separated and migrated out of sequence.
  - ANB Convention, Hoonah, October 13, 1976, Tape 451.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR337)
    Description of contents: Sides A and B.
  - ANB Convention, Hoonah, October 13, 1976, Tape 452.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR338)
    Description of contents: Sides C and D.
  - ANB Convention, Hoonah, October 13, 1976, Tape 453.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR339)
    Description of contents: Sides E and F.
  - ANB Convention, Hoonah, October 13, 1976, Tape 454.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR340)
    Description of contents: Sides G and H? "Note: #474, Andrew Johnny may be part of the same convention, but a different day. Welcome speech and peace dance. Dancers: Harry Marvin, William Johnson, delegates from Hoonah, Haines, Yakutat, and Klukwan camps. Singers: Elsie Pratt (also drum), Katherine Mills, Mrs. Wilson, Amy Marvin, Nora Dauenhauer, Margaret McKinley, Lillian Hammond."
  - Olaf Abraham. Aan Tlein, 1971, Tape 455.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR341)
    Description of contents: "Copied for Richard Dauenhauer by Elaine Abraham Ramos, in 1971 from a reel-to-reel tape in the Abraham collection. Part of the narrative leading up to and including the song was transcribed and published in Doo Goojee Yeenaa-dei, Tlingit Language Workshop Reader, 1972, pp 15-18."
  - Olaf Abraham 40 Day Party (Yakutat?), ca. 1971-1972, Tape 456.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR342)
  - David Abraham, Wake and dinner, October 28, 1972, Tape 457.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR343)
    Description of contents: Yakutat.
  - David Abraham Funeral, October 29, 1972, Tape 458.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR344)
  - Yakutat, October 30, 1972, Tape 459.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR345)
    Description of contents: Recorded in conjunction with David Abraham funeral.
  - Tlingit-Haida, `, Tape 460.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR346)
  - L'uknax.ádi ku.éex' (Potlatch), October 13, 1988, Tape 461.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR347)
    Description of contents: Juneau ANB.
  - Thunderbird House, Klukwan, May 5, 1972, Tape 462.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR348)
    Description of contents: "Note: Beginning is yéik."
  - Unidentified content, undated, Tape 463.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR349)
    Description of contents: "Possibly a continuation of #462. Has "2" on label."
  - Gajaa Héen Dancers, tape 1, October 7, 1976, Tape 464.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR350)
    Description of contents: Sitka ANB Hall.
  - Gajaa Héen Dancers, tape 2, October 7, 1976, Tape 465.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR351)
  - Mary Pelayo. Songs, May 13, 1973, Tape 466.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR352)
    Description of contents: Sitka. In Russian, English, Filipino.
  - Russian Church, November 7, 1976, Tape 467.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR353)
  - Consecration of the Russian Orthodox Cathedral in Sitka (?), tape 1, undated, Tape 468.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR354)
    Description of contents: "Note: side numberings may be wrong. #468 has I, IV; #469 has III, II. Or side 1 was recorded, the tape replaced for sides 2 & 3, and the original tape inserted for the last side."
  - Consecration of the Russian Orthodox Cathedral in Sitka (?), tape 2, undated, Tape 469.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR355)
  - Unidentified Orthodox Service, Tape V, undated, Tape 470.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR356)
    Description of contents: "'End of Service.' Beginning of sequence missing, unless it is 468-469."
  - Basket Weaving Workshop, Haines, October 6, 1983, Tape 471.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR357)
    Description of contents: Austin Hammond's party.
  - Unidentified recording in conjunction with the Haines event of October 1983 (Tape 471), 1983, Tape 472.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR358)
  - ANB Convention, Haines, 1975, Tape 473.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR359)
    Description of contents: "$10,000 was donated by Aunty Jenny Marks. Horace Marks narration."
  - Andrew Johnny, welcome address to delegates, October 11, 1976, Tape 474.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR360)
    Description of contents: "(Probably Hoonah, and part of the events recorded on #451-454 sequence)"
  - Horace Marks on heritage; re: museum idea for Raven house and clan collection, undated, Tape 475.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR361)
    Description of contents: Haines.
  - Practice at Austin Hammond's, tape 1, undated, Tape 476.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR362)
    Description of contents: "Side 1: Friday. Side 2: Saturday morning at Austin's. Evening at ANB Hall. No date. (When doing metadata look for clues: is this in conjunction with the Haa Shagoon filming in August 1980, or in the context of one of Austin's potlatches)"
  - Practice at Austin Hammond's, tape 2, undated, Tape 477.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR363)
    Description of contents: Saturday evening at ANB Hall.
  - Haines, May 1973?, 1973-05, Tape 478.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR364)
    Description of contents: Sides 1 and 2. Songs by Johnny and Jenny Marks.
  - Haines, May 1973?, May, 1973, Tape 479.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR365)
    Description of contents: Sides 3 and 4. Songs by Johnny and Jenny Marks.
  - Haines, May 24, 1973, at Austin Hammond's, May 24, 1973, Tape 480.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR366)
    Description of contents: Side 2: 6-25-73.
  - Haines, ANB Hall, June 29, 1973, Tape 481.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR367)
    Description of contents: Aunty Jenny Marks. Side 2: Haines, Geesán Dancers, Dalton Days.
  - Haines, June 29, 1973, Tape 482.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR368)
    Description of contents: Side 1: Fish?? ANB Hall. Side 2; Dalton Trail.
  - Haines, June 29, 1973, Tape 483.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR369)
    Description of contents: Austin Hammond's house (Raven House).
  - Austin's and Auntie's Party, Haines, tape 1, August 28, 1970, Tape 484.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR370)
    Description of contents: "Note: There are 3 tapes in this sequence. 484 side A = "No. I." Side B = "No. 2." #485 side A is also labeled "No. I," so either 484 or 485 may be the first.
  - Austin's and Auntie's Party, Haines, tape 2, August 28, 1970, Tape 485.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR371)
  - Austin's and Auntie's Party, Haines, tape 3, August 28, 1970, Tape 486.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR372)
    Description of contents: "Side B is labeled 'last.'"
  - Jenny Marks Funeral, January 22, 1976, Tape 487.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR373)
    Description of contents: Starting at ANB Hall.
  - Jenny Marks Funeral, continued, January 22-23, 1976, Tape 488.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR374)
    Description of contents: Side 1: ANS service, Jan. 22, 1976; Presbyterian service, Jan. 23, 1976. Side 2: Salvation Army Service, Friday, Jan. 23, 1976.
  - Aunty Jennie's Funeral Service, January 22-23, 1976, Tape 489.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR375)
    Description of contents: Raven House.
  - Jennie's (Funeral) Ceremony at Austin's (Raven House), January 22-23, 1976, Tape 490.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR376)
  - Jenny / Potlatch, undated, Tape 491.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR377)
    Description of contents: "Note: The tape is labeled only '#5.' The box is labeled 'Jenny /Potlatch.' It is unclear how or if this tape fits in with the rest of the following sequence 492-499."
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch. Rehearsal, tape 1, September 24, 1976, Tape 492.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR378)
    Description of contents: Friday evening at Austin Hammond's (Raven House). Rehearsal, planning, playing old tapes.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch. Rehearsal, tape 2, September 24, 1976, Tape 493.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR379)
    Description of contents: Rehearsal continued.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 1, September 25, 1976, Tape 494.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR380)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 1, sides 1 and 2.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 2, September 25, 1976, Tape 495.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR381)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 2, sides 3 and 4.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 3, September 25, 1976, Tape 496.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR382)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 3, sides 5 and 6.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 4, September 25, 1976, Tape 497.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR383)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 4, sides 7 and 8.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 5, September 25, 1976, Tape 498.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR384)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 5, side 9. Note: side B is labeled as empty. Go to tape 6, side A for side 10 of potlatch.
  - Jenny Marks Potlatch, tape 6, September 25, 1976, Tape 499.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR385)
    Description of contents: Haines ANB Hall Tape 6, side 10. Conclusion of potlatch.
  - Unidentified, undated, Tape 500.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR386)
    Description of contents: "Possibly Walter Soboleff? No date. The original cassette has multiple labeling none of which seems to be correct; the tape was probably reused. Existing labeling has Nicene Creed in Tlingit, Dukt'ootl, and Frank Johnson, but what I listened to sounds like possibly Walter Soboleff, and it mentions his name and growing up in Killisnoo and Angoon."
  - Mary Rudolph (?) and Amy Marvin singing Chookaneidi songs at the request of the grandchildren of Chookaneidi, undated, Tape 501.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR387)
    Description of contents: "Request that it not be disbursed far and wide, but only among the clan grandchildren and with recognition of clan ownership."
  - Austin Hammond telling Raven and Fog and Raven and Water, May, 1989, Tape 502.; 1 sound cassette: analog (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR388)
    Description of contents: "Excerpt copied from Rasmussen Conference tapes, May 1989. See #416-422 for the full conference sequence."
  - George Davis, 1960, Tape 70.; 1 sound tape reel: analog; 5 in. (Item-id AFC 2019/004: SR389)
    Description of contents: "Making plans for someone who died. He (George Davis) is telling the people, there is a certain way to handle this. He (the important deceased) didn't set a good example of how to do this, though. George then tells how it is on the English side, tells of it in Tlingit. How they built the ANB hall in Angoon. Then how they built a road to the graveyard (from ANB?). He says we are gonna fold away (put up) our culture for a while. He tells of the flood 6000 years ago, then the people came down. Those that are L'uknax.ádi came out by Dry Bay whose crest is L'ook (Coho). Mark 00:40:00 switch to English, and tells where he and his relatives come from, and where they have been. Mark 00:46:00 continues in Tlingit."